Now we'll go back to the
idea of ​​where that voice in
your head comes from
.  And if you don't remember
anything at all, for example, if your friend asks
what you studied
last weekend, you can't just say, "
I don't remember
anymore."  That thing said that
the voice in your head
isn't
you, and you really don't have a
choice about what the words in your head say
.
If you're
depressed, if your relationship is
falling
apart, you know that you can't
tell your mind to stop talking
about something.  So feel
free to embrace
this idea.  It means you have no control over
who is talking in your mind, and that person is
n't
you.  Because those words
are spoken before you hear
them.
By the time you hear
those words, consider them to have become a thing of the
past
forever.  So where did those words come
from
?  It comes from the seeds in
your mind
.  And as our friend
said, those seeds
have been sown by you.
And no one else can tell you
what you're thinking in your mind
.  You also can't say that you
have to think
just as little as other people.
Only when you have
good intentions in your mind will
those words be truly
amazing.
They will give you
new ideas and you will be happy for the rest of your life
.  And if you don't learn
how to control the
process, it's just the same as before
you came to this program
.  Almost everyone in the
world sows seeds
by chance.
They didn't even know they were planting the
same seeds
.  And then when those seeds
sprout, they have thoughts in
their minds,
and they have no control
over that for their entire lives
.  YES.  From the time you were a child until
now.
It's not you
[the music]
saying it, and you don't have a choice at
this moment about what the voice is
saying in your mind.
You have a choice for
next week; you can sow some
special seeds,
and then next week
your voice will sound
amazing.  It's amazing that
we can live in a mind where the
speaker is so
interesting.  And each coming week is
better than the last.  Once you know
how to plant the
seed, it's like a devil, it's
like a joy that
never ends
.  When you can see
that immediately.
So, that one-million-
dollar company in
Manhattan is now $250 million, and I got out of
that 25 years ago.  Well, that was just the
beginning of the
fun, and then it got even
more fun because I knew
how to plant the seed of the
conversational partner in my mind
.  And then he always tells me how
wonderful it would be if
we went back to
Mexico City next year.
[Music]
The thing you learned
this weekend about how to plant a
seed.  Can I repeat the steps
?
And then, if we have more time
[for music],
I'll give you a little
headache from these stanzas.  And if
we still have
time, could we have a question
and answer session?  So
if you have any questions,
be prepared.
Now we're going to go through the
images because images
help us remember things more easily
.  And I know who Patr and that
big boss, that fourth boss, are.  That
's
Santi.  Oh, their child.
I'm sure they'll
have follow-up programs,
programs after
this one, to explain
those images over and over again
.  So this is the first time,
and they will give it to you.  So, would
you like to use the same picture
?  Alright.
Do we have enough money with $100?   I'm
serious
.  We still have enough money to sell the music tonight,
right?  Okay.  100
dollars.  What's going on in
this picture?
And by
the way, 50 dollars for what happens in
this picture and 50 dollars for what
doesn't happen in this picture
[music]
.  The woman in
this painting is planting a
seed that will grow into a
tree.  What does this tree represent
?
She had planted the seed
long ago in her mind
.  It represents the voice in
her mind, doesn't it
?  So what isn't happening
in
this picture?  Can she... can she not eat it
?
It came from her wish,
not because she ate it,
okay?
I'm going to show you a strange picture
.  Well, that's because people remember those
strange pictures.  They don't remember
ordinary pictures.
When you think about this week's bag
, just remember this picture,
okay
?  I want to plant a
voice in my mind that will enter my consciousness
and give me great ideas, just like
the way I
started my diamond business
.  We started with $7.
But the person in
my mind, in the
diamond business, we have a
very special word that means '
n', which means '
nhi', so I have that voice
in my mind.  Let's go into the
diamond business!  I'm in the diamond business.
And isn't that amazing?
It was the largest jewelry company
in the
world.  So, if you develop
your
voice, it will be very interesting.  So,
this
will be the next picture.
You have
10. Okay.  How about $100 per picture
?
Don't raise your hand before I ask the
question.
Well, this picture represents
that there are many
choices.  But what you learn here
is the
best.  You will be the one to choose.
Conveniently, there's a special system
where he chooses you and you give
him $50 after the class.
That particular system is about sowing
good seeds in order to cultivate
good ideas.
[Music]
and conversely, if
we sow bad seeds,
we won't have
good voices in our heads that can lead to
financial freedom and
good family relationships
.  You can choose from many
different voices, and I chose the
voice that conveys creativity; it's the
best.  You could say it's the voice
for
new ideas.  Because that voice can be
used for all
other voices.  Yeah, I have a new idea for
making money.
I have a new idea: how about making the
wife do the cooking and washing the
dishes, or maybe the husband
?  Think about that.  I think
my wife has already done that
.  If you are very
creative, you can be creative in
many different ways.  So,
in
this class, we are focusing on the
seed for creativity in
speech—creative speech in
our minds.  So please don't forget just the
picture,
okay?  If you're smart, you
'll raise your hand right now.
I was just kidding.
Next picture?
Ho th and
Andre para tener buenas ideas lo mejor
es asistir a clases de cosas que no
[music]
entiendes.  We have
good ideas, and the best thing we do
is go into classes where you
don't understand anything at all.
I don't mean for you to go into every single
class that you don't understand.  But
the easy offer was that we had
three free classes every week,
and those were classes on
interpreting.
They are
difficult, and it is these difficult things that
make you strong.  If
you've ever trained birds, you'll
know.  Don't worry if you don't
understand
everything or if you can't understand anything at all;
it's not a problem.  Just
sit
there and listen.
And the process doesn't follow
a straight line like this.  It
goes like this.  Up and down, up and down, up and down,
up and down.  Is
that okay?   There
will be times when you
fail, you'll stop attending classes for
three weeks, and then you'll come
back.  Meditation is the
same.  The idea
of ​​watching Netflix, Netflix, Netflix,
then meditating, meditating, meditating,
then Netflix, then doing business again,
it's a feasible way for
us to go straight up that path
.  Never, ever even
think about that.  YES.  YES.  You
'll mess things up every
month.  Your patience in
not getting angry is the same.
Patience, patience, patience.  Then
someone drives over your car, and it
falls down, and then you have to be patient, patient,
patient, and it falls down again, and then you have to be
patient, patient, patient again.
Nobody is perfect.
If you were already perfect, you would
n't need to come to
this class.  And that means that sometimes
you're going to mess things up
[music]
.  Be prepared for that and
don't take it too seriously.
Oh, I guess I completely forgot about my meditation practice
.  It's OK.
Can you meditate tomorrow?   Okay
.  Are you ready for the next picture
?  This picture is very easy, is
n't it?
[Music]
If you are under 21, you must use
this money for
your college scholarship.
These are
pouches where you can put your electronic devices,
and they have a time lock
so you can avoid being distracted by
electronic devices and
get a really good night's sleep.
If you go with me after
we finish
this talk, I'll give
you a bag as a
gift, okay?
[music]
It's both a zip-up bag and a
pouch that you can
wear over it.  It's really
cute.  It's my favorite thing
in my entire life.   It's
okay if you forget to see your teacher.  I'll give this to
you, and then your friends can give me
another Sim tree, okay?
[Music]
Are you guys ready?   Next
step, what's the next image?
[Music]
Before you
answer, this picture has a
connection to the previous one.
Work in order to
experience the answer. That's a
wrong answer, but it's a
good answer.  That means that in order to read a book,
you need concentration and you need to
put electronic devices in your
bag.  So
I want to say that before I
started the "Good Sleep,
Good Sleep Reading" club,
I had to stop reading
physical books because I had problems with
putting all the books in my
phone, but I
still enjoyed reading before
bed.
Because when I read books on
my phone, I don't sleep
well with [music].  But if I read a physical book for
10 to 15 minutes, I'll sleep very
soundly.
Okay, regarding the time lock, my suggestion
is
from 10:00 PM to 6:00
AM when I'm
traveling and I'm alone in the
hotel, which is a very dangerous place.
I knew I couldn't trust
myself to lock the time lock,
so I asked my friend for help
.  He would come to my room and knock on the
door at 10
o'clock, and I'd say, "
Okay, the computer?"  Here's the phone
.  And then I kind of got a
good night's sleep.  YES.   And what about the
hotel's TV remote control,
sir?  Rub.
Teacher, your room has two
remotes, that's enough
[for the music]
.  I don't know
.  If you implement
this system, you'll double your efficiency
and what?
You could buy some eye makeup,
or you could get eight hours of sleep.  YES.
in a personal way
.  I think a woman who
sleeps 5
hours and uses a lot of
eye makeup [music] looks very similar to
a woman who sleeps 8 hours.
But getting eight hours of sleep makes it look
more natural, and it's the cheapest makeup product
.  You can go to
Sephora.  If she wants to
go to Sephora, then make up a
reason to
refuse because you can't possibly go out
there.  without spending at least
$300.  Take her to the pharmacy and get that
stuff; it only costs $3
.  It will change your appearance
and it will make your mind
incredibly powerful.
You could make double the
money and you'd never know it because
you've never done
it.  I'm not saying that sleeping 8
hours a night will change your income
.  But if you do that
for three
weeks, your mind will become
stronger and you will feel extremely healthy.
I am the
grandfather.  I've been to
yoga classes and there were kids who were 20 years old
.  And I was like, wow.
Just think of it as getting a
good night's sleep and disconnecting from those phones
.  Let's give it 16
hours and then dedicate 8 hours to
yourself, okay?
The phone is supposed to
save you time, but instead it
just takes it away
.  So please, please, please try
that.  If you don't have the strength
to do it yourself,
ask a friend for help.
He bought a house next door to
mine.  He used to live
thousands of miles away from me.  Now it's
only about two minutes to get to my house
.  When my wife goes on vacation, for example,
he'll knock on the door at 10:00, he
'll come to my house,
and at
10:00, there's always a
friend.  If you're like
me, and you don't have the strength to
do it yourself, then you need a
friend to help you.
The phone is very much like
alcohol.  We're all
addicted to
it.  Where is our favorite place to
use our phones?  I was sitting
in a special chair, in a
special room.
After an hour, it was
my wife who knocked on the
door.  There are two other people in
this house who also need to use the toilet,
you know
?  I apologize for
this news about Mr. Trump.  So please be
careful,
okay?  Perhaps you don't have enough
strength to do that.
Instead of doing it yourself, ask a
friend for help; you can help
each other out and you'll never regret
it.  You will become a much more successful person
.  Please do that.
I think Mono, KFC, and
Apple are going to assassinate me because I
gave you that offer.  What's the
next picture
[with music]?
I like having a mix
of paper books when I
go to sleep.
Sometimes I feel like I
could read a slightly more profound book,
so I'd read a book about the
Diamond Cutter Sutra
.  And sometimes I feel tired
in the evening.  That's why when you
go to bed, I'll read something like
the book "The Garden."  Therefore, I
will keep two
books.  One book is
a bit more profound and insightful, while the other is
more relaxing.  And with this book, you'll
fall asleep in just
minutes.  Even if you read it in the
morning, you'll fall asleep right away.   Okay
.  Next picture?
I didn't show
this picture.  I was supposed to show
you this picture yesterday.
But I didn't have a projector.  That was
the last picture from
yesterday.  And I told you there's
a special method for
planting the seed of your
inner voice.  And by the way, this guy
did just
that.
Okay, you choose
.  Camisa
[music]
verde.  The seed doubles in size every
24 hours.
So that it can show me what
I am
seeing.  This class has been
a lot of fun these past three days.
Why? Because Michael didn't teach
you a new meditation exercise, and
if you don't do it, you'll feel
more guilty than
last week.  Everyone likes to
feel guilty.  I feel the same way
.  Well, I have a student who
told me, "Teacher, please don't
teach me any more meditation exercises
."  I asked why?
Yes.  Because I would have felt even
more guilty if I hadn't
practiced the meditation exercise that you taught me
earlier.  Now, if the teacher teaches me a
new lesson and I don't practice it, I
feel even
more guilty.  So,
you can take this picture
anywhere and no one will know that
you're actually meditating.
Someone might think she's deep in
thought.  He's thinking about a girl,
but he's not thinking about
that in the conventional sense.  He was wondering
what kind of seed he had sown
last week to create this guy.
I had a
good day.  I've already driven to
work.  Suddenly the radio played a
Jimmy Hendrick song and I was so
happy.  And then some guy cut
in front of
my car.  And think about that.  Go ahead and
do your meditation
.
Try this meditation exercise to create
the creative voice in your head
.  What kind of seed did I sow
to create this idiot?
Think about that.
And then, just like you go to work, get out of the
car, and forget about it
.  That's a short one-
minute meditation, three times a day, five times a
day.  Teacher, what time should I
meditate when something stupid
happens?
And meditate when something good
happens.  I guess I met the
most amazing person in Mexico City.
Oh, that's really great
[music]
.  What did I do
?  Okay.   Is that okay
?  Those are the things that
trigger your meditation
.  Something happens when something
bad happens, something good
happens, then you ask yourself why
me?  My teacher taught me in a
lot of strange ways.
All day long
things tell me to scrub toilets, I'll learn
something.
The teacher bought a television.
The monk said that he was the abbot of the monastery, so
he was allowed to watch TV, while I, as his disciple, was
not.  But I was like, "
But the teacher said it's about
humanity."  But if there's anything
interesting on TV, the teacher will ring the
bell.
You might wonder why we assume that the
teachers have the bell, right?  That's
the
TV bell.  When you hear the bell,
run upstairs; there's
something interesting for
you there.  And I was like, "Yes, yes, yes, sir."  And
I work near the staircase,
looking up like this.  Tiny tiny tiny
.  And then I ran up onto the embankment.
And the teacher said to watch the
news.  And then there was this woman, and
her house was
burned down.  She was doing
something and caused the house to burn down.  And then
she cried, asking why me, and
why everyone else was doing the same thing,
but me?  Why did
my house catch fire?
And then the teacher said, "You can go
now."
I just asked why he was taking it
from me, he said, "
Go ahead," and I went, and I continued
working, and then he kept going, little by little, little by little,
after an hour I
ran up again, thinking, "Look at this!"
Then there was a handsome guy on
TV
knocking on the door of a poor man in a
terrible neighborhood in New York.
And then a poor woman opened the
door.  And then he
said, and he said, "She's the
winner of this lottery, it's
$5 million."
And then they showed her picture on
TV and she was like this
and she was dancing
and then the teacher asked
me why she didn't ask
why it was me when you win the
lottery, nobody says 'why
me, why
me?'  But when your house catches fire,
you ask, "Why me?"  Why
me?  If you're on a team that's focused on
creative voice acting, you'll be
asking yourself, "Why me?"
You'll always ask that question.  When
something bad
happens, it's natural to
ask yourself, "Why me?"  But
even when something good happens,
I'll still ask myself, "Why me?"
By the way
[music],
by the way, did you notice
that I didn't ask you
what you needed to think about?
I just want to ask the question and
how to answer it.  It's up to
you, it's your problem.  I'm just asking
you so you can answer.  When
something good happens, when
something bad happens, just ask yourself
why me, and then you
'll answer in your own way.
I don't think this meditation will
take you more than two or three
minutes.  Because that's just how your life is
.  You can't sit there for two
hours and think about
why that bastard would cut off
the front of his car.
We don't have that much time,
but we can have 30
seconds, and maybe we can answer
that question then.  You know
the seed is in your mind
.
Okay, let's get back to the
[music],
which is the next picture.
Oh, that's the last picture, I guess I've run
out of money.
Okay, you don't need to concentrate
anymore.  Why me?  Why
me?
I'll go over the meaning so I can see what
time it is.
Okay, let's go through a few parts of
the
reading to get a feel for it
.
And then we'll finish with
the question and answer section.  I will read
the Tibetan part to wish
you good luck.
Word teacher, please come up here.  Today, the teacher
will
[read] [music]
just read, okay?  It's as
if I'm not staying
here.  Read it in a sweet way.
By the way,
he's the best Tibetan language teacher
.
He teaches Tibetan for free every
week.  And if you don't attend
his class, that's
crazy.  It's free, it's
fun.  He knows how to teach
people to read very quickly.   It's
even better than what I could
do myself.  So don't be crazy enough to skip
his class
.  Give the chair back
.  Thank you.
This is the
translation of "About the Pen".  Okay.  It's about the story of the
pen.  If this pen truly came from the
pen itself,
it would never
change, it would never run out of
ink.  If the ink is coming from the
pen's side,
it will never run out of ink.
But if the pen comes from
me, if it comes from my seed,
then whenever I use the
pen, who will it become
?  What's that guy's name?
Every time you use the
pen, the ink will gradually run out.
It's not that the ink has run
out, but rather that you're using up all
your seeds
.  Do I have any money left?
Where is my bank
?  Okay.  How about another 100 dollars
?  You will explain to my wife
why we're out of money.
This is a tough question.  The
big question is, when you write with a
pen and you write
something...  So where did that inscription come from
?  Don't do it like this.  Doing
so would essentially earn you more money.
The writing itself also comes from
my seeds.  Good.  Here's a $100 gift for
you.  This is very difficult, is
n't it?
People say, "Teacher, the pen
exists on its own
."  And then I said, "Why is
this guy able to write on paper?"
But the writing itself doesn't come from a
pen
.  When you move the
pen, your mind creates the
writing on the
paper.  Now you have some bad news.
Why?   For
each minute you watch the
next movie, which direction is the information coming from
?  Teacher, I want to watch
the
Deadpool werewolf movie.
And by the way, my system
is like my meditation practice;
you can go into it, watch a movie, and
you can meditate.  Why do you consider
this person so stupid?
What did I do?  Who wrote that
movie?  You wrote the movie.
Every minute of the movie,
your mind creates that image.  Do
n't forget
that.  And then everything gets old
.  Why are there some movies that leave
you feeling so happy when they end?
I am very happy.  Finally,
that movie has ended
.  I felt I had to stay
because I had paid, but
I didn't like the
movie.  When that movie ended,
I told my wife, "I'm so
happy that the movie is
over."  Why did that movie end
like that?
Because you've essentially run out of seeds
for that.  Your seeds are
all
gone.  And that seed tastes delicious
to your body too
.  Your body was created
in your mother's womb by a
seed.  It begins with the chakras
first, and then the sutras.
And then the bones will surround the
meridians, and then the flesh will surround the
bones.  Throughout the weeks you spend
inside your mother's womb, 36
weeks.  Each week will essentially be a
different rotation of the bicycles
.  And then you'll be finished.
All of those things come from
seeds.  As you
use your body, the seed
gradually disappears.  If this pen came from its own source, there
's no reason to consider
it to have run out of ink.  I'll repeat it now.
If the pen comes from its own source,
it will never run out of ink
.  If the film doesn't come
from
your side, it will remain there
forever.  But if it comes from your seed,
it will gradually wither and eventually
die
.  Now, here's the question.
We can borrow some
money.  Teacher W has all the money
that he considers to have won
in the past.  This might be
the child who's cost me the most money.
In
this book, in this poem, there is
a discussion, a
debate between two
beings: an angel and a demon.
Sometimes in a poem, an
angel speaks, and sometimes in a poem, a
devil
speaks.  And who said this stanza is worth
$100?  And that's
why it's an angel.  Why is that?
She said it was an angel speaking.  So why then
?
Because, because,
because, because the angel is
explaining why everything gets
old, explaining why
your recent relationship fell
apart, okay?
And that's
good advice, so it has to be an angel,
right?  100 dollars for her.
We'll go through two more stanzas and then
we'll get to the question and
answer section.   Come up here
.  He's the second best bass player
in this room.
Oh,
thereang
mi
ngaji ng chú
[music]
ngel are you ready?  Spanish,
now I can read this in
my reading material
.   Okay
.  Okay.
Good.  If nothing comes from a
seed, then nothing can be
mine.
Money, even if it were your mouth, could never truly
be your mouth.  That nose ca
n't be your nose either
.  That stomach can't be your stomach either
.
The house cannot be your house
.  Your husband or wife
cannot be yours, and neither
can
your children.  If they didn't come from
seeds, then things that don't come from
seeds can't possibly be yours,
right?
Anything that doesn't come from a seed can
never be yours, never will
be yours.  Now it's deeper
.  Things, absolutely everything, that don't
come from seeds can't possibly germinate and
combine with other things.
My tree is my grandchild.
You say you have a connection
with this child, but
without the
seed, there would be no
connection at all.
If my tree originated from
him, then it belongs to it, and
it couldn't possibly have come from its mother
.  It couldn't possibly have come from the mother of
[the music]
.  Only something that comes from a
seed can come from
another person.  If the
pen had come from its own side,
I would never have been able to own
it.
Because it didn't come from my seeds
.  Because the connection also comes
from my seed
.  When I lose that connection,
it also stems from my own seed
.  If everything it has doesn't
come from the seed, it will never grow
old.  If everything didn't come from a
seed, no one could have it.
You need to think about that
[musical] thing
.  A world that doesn't originate from
seeds is
impossible.  A seed, a pen, that does
n't come from a seed
can never be considered to have run out of
sap.  You can't buy a
pen and assume it doesn't come from a
seed.
Sometimes you need a pen and
your friend gives it to
you.  Sometimes you need a pen and you
go to the store and they say, "Sorry, we're
out of pens."  You don't have a pen from
that store.  You get the pen from
the seed.
You need to share everything
you
have, and then you will have
more.  And then the Lord said that
over and over again.  Yes, the Lord
Jesus also spoke about that
many times.  Those are wonderful things
.  What you want, you should give
to others.
If someone takes your sweater,
get their phone number and
ask them if they want
my sweater too.
If someone taps
this side of your face, it's like telling them that
this side also really wants to be
tapped
.   Okay
.  Rob, are you ready
?  Do we have enough boats to get back home
?  Do we have enough gas to get home
?  We can provide
credit.  Who wrote this stanza
?  I know the correct answer is
you, but is it an angel or a devil
speaking?
And why
is it an
angel, but never take it as
answering the question, or leaving a
question mark.  You need to say it with confidence,
it must be an angel.  Why is that?
Speaking
of it coming from a
seed, you have a picture with a girl and a
tree in
it.  Never forget this girl
.  Seeds.
If we're talking about seeds, would
n't it be angels
?  Demons don't like to talk about
seeds.  Okay, where is she?   Okay
.  Okay.  Finally, here we go
.  I think it would be great if
we had Gipson up
here.  Giipson is a
fantastic translator from Taiwan, an
amazing translator
.  I don't understand
why he's doing what he's doing in Mexico, but
I'm happy with it.
[Music]
And I also want to welcome
his partner,
Miss, and Mr. Gipsin, who is especially dedicated to
those so-called pocket-sized books of Dharma,
and he has already completed two
books, and those are
600-year-old books.  And the idea was about
a little book that you could put
in your pocket.
The translations from Mr. Word and the
translations from the
team will be very good.  If you have
an argument with your teacher or
your husband, you can
use it like this.  It's very
thick and heavy like
this.  I'm going to smash this on your head
.  But the books that
Mr. Kon translated are the kind of books
we call pocket-sized
.   Once he
finishes this book,
he'll start the
next one soon
.  Let's begin
.  And by the way, for many
years he also called upon demons to
help the Guahera group.
To help second-generation refugees
move from Central America to the U.S. border
.
They have a very nice guesthouse there where
people can shower,
relax, have some
food, and then return to the
ship. They've been supporting that for
over 10 years now.
Don't worry, I won't ask
you.  This is for Taiwanese people.
The team here wanted to give them
this box,
and every night they would put
a little bit of loose change into it, and that way they
've raised hundreds of thousands of dollars, and they've
supported the team a lot in
translating books
into Spanish.   Let's try again
.  Thank you for your hard work
.  Thank you.
Okay, let's read it in Spanish and
then we'll talk about
it.  We're down two minutes now,
okay?  The same goes for
my bank account
.  Alright
.  Let me explain for just a
second
.  If you
join the South American teacher team that teaches
ACI, please let Andrew know.
And you could say it like
this.  When
you do the teaching you do in
Costa
Rica, I'll take people's hands
and lead them nowhere.
And
then I'll teach them a special meditation exercise
.  Don't think about anything
.  And then we teach them that
when they
meditate, they should think as much as
possible.  I will make it into a
true form of meditation.   Who
is speaking?  Who's
speaking?  And then we will complete
that—that is the devil.
All
right.
Diablo diblo.  Okay.
[Laughter]
Everyone asked, "Teacher, why have
n't you been to Mexico City for so long?"
And then they said, "Why did you come
back? Because I missed it. I
missed it when I went to
the big church in
Mexico City, next to the
euro bakery, and it was very
religious."  I would love to go to church, is
that okay?
Thank you and see you
next year.